Little Monster,
you've outdone yourself with that stunt.
The media storm boosted sales
of Dark Fairy Tale to 150 million on the first day.
I saved you hundreds of millions in marketing costs.
Don't you know?
Those who play with fire
will eventually get burned.
A hungry wolf in the desert
would lick scorpion venom,
let alone roast meat
roasting by the bonfire?
What a pity.
If you were my daughter,
now
you would be ringing the bell on NASDAQ.
I'll take it as a compliment.
It's getting late.
I'll pack my luggage and leave you to rest.
Since you've moved in,
just stay here.
I won't bother you anymore.
You should also get some rest early.
Older people are prone to irregular heartbeats.
You need to stay healthy to deal with things later on.
One last question.
What exactly do you want?
Shares?
A title?
Or the lives of my children?
As long as future in-law relations are harmonious.
After all, you still need to keep your body healthy
to teach your grandchildren to sing the family genealogy song.
The Rh-negative blood type
belongs to autosomal recessive inheritance.
That means both parents
must carry the recessive gene to have children with panda blood.
If both parents have panda blood,
a 25% chance of inheriting the blood type,
and a 50% chance of maintaining the normal blood type.
When did you come back?
When I got back to the venue,
they said you had already left.
Our mom is back.
I know.
But Uncle Wu said she went to bed early.
So I didn't disturb her.
What did you talk about?
She was already asleep when I got back.
The kindergarten teacher complained to me
that Mumu couldn't draw his dad's face in art class.
I've been too busy with work recently.
I don't have much time to be with him.
But fortunately,
you and Liu take care of him.
But children
need their father's companionship.
The Dark Fairy Tale thing is over.
I'll pick up Mumu in a few days.
It's getting late.
Get some rest.
Qianqian,
Jiang Li said some crazy things in the live streaming room today.
Actually...
Do you remember what blood type Mumu is?
O.
Mumu's blood type is O.
Why do you ask me this?
Qianqian,
if you still love me,
don't say anything else.
Good night.
What's this?
This is wild vegetable from my hometown.
Young Master loves them the most.
Throw it away.
These are all homemade.
Very clean.
Mom,
I have work at the company later.
I'm leaving now.
Zhou Jian,
after you get to the company,
hand over your current work.
Take a long vacation for yourself.
You're so tired that
you can't even remember the title.
Yes, sir.
Grandma is back.
Grandma.
Mumu,
do you miss me?
Yes.
Did you study hard in kindergarten?
Mumu can recite nursery rhymes very well.
Good.
Recite one for me.
OK.
What do you call your father's father?
Grandfather.
What do you call your father's mother?
Grandmother.
What do you call your mother's father?
Grandfather.
What do you call your mom's mom?
I call her...
Grandma.
Why did you stop?
You're my mom's mom.
I should call you Grandma.
But why do you want me to call you Grandma?
Because
I'm your grandma.
Mom,
I'll take Mumu to school.
You stay at home and reflect on yourself
for a while.
Wu, get the car ready.
Yes, ma'am.
Yan,
my wild vegetable lunch box.
Mumu,
wild vegetables will upset your stomach.
When you get off school,
I'll take you to eat
cream cake,
okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Auntie,
two servings of jianbing.
Would you like to add anything?
What is this?
This is wild vegetable.
Give me one.
Okay.
It's very delicious.
Have a try.
Dark Fairy Tale made a miracle on the first day of sales.
But netizens don't think
this is just a marketing plan.
Is the internal strife of Golden Thread Fashion Group
real or fake?
Thank you.
Will there be a new reversal later?
We will continue to follow up.
Hope you can like and follow us.
Thank you.
I didn't expect you to like spicy gluten.
This spicy gluten is delicious.
Don't you know that in the rich family,
spicy gluten is a symbol of poor people?
My grandfather said
in the famine years,
people could even find sweetness in tree bark.
People live so long,
Pretending decency is more ridiculous than eating spicy gluten.
Elder Shen is really a casual person.
I'll take you to meet him next time.
You two must get along well.
By the way,
you were right about your suspicion last time.
Zhou Jian
did go to the alliance of sisters-in-law.
Now that things have gotten so big,
netizens won't believe that you're just telling a story.
How are you going to wrap this up?
Why should I end it?
The netizens love gossip.
The heat will last until the end.
But this will also make you
the target of multiple parties.
Even if I protect you,
it's hard to swallow the golden thread.
I didn't say I wanted to swallow it.
I want to make soup with it
and invite everyone to a funeral banquet.
I found some information in the Young Master's car.
I've sent them to you.
Young Master's car accident might just be a coincidence.
How did Lu Xu know?
Not sure yet.
But I feel
someone wants to bring that up.
Investigate Jiang Li thoroughly.
I always feel
this girl is not simple.
Investigate thoroughly.
Handle properly.
Make sure there are no traces of that.
Okay.
Give me some time.
Old Wu,
thank you
for your hard work over the years.
It's my duty.
You can tell Mumu
that his biological father
is a scoundrel who is madly in love with his mother.
Hello.
What's up?
Miss Lu.
I want to see you.
Now.
Okay.
I'll send you the address.
Mu Chen often says that
a younger sister is like a wild vine.
But now it seems that
you are better at strangling prey than a wild vine.
Are you complimenting me for being better than my teacher,
or are you here to repent
and see how tall the grass on her grave has grown?
You have her stubbornness in your eyes.
Yes, we do.
But there's a colder fire in your pupils.
So, do you love me for these eyes that resemble hers,
or for this fire that can burn you and the Lu family?
I've liked her since high school.
But because of my background at that time,
I never had the courage.
But later, fortunately,
I found
that she had feelings for me.
When I was in college,
we met again
and became a couple.
I used to dream that
if I were rich,
I would buy her a big diamond ring
and propose to her like a knight
welcoming a princess
like a knight welcomes a princess.
But the reality is that
we can squeeze into a
one-bedroom apartment
and eat instant noodles together.
That's also a very happy thing.
Now I have the ability to do it.
I have the ability.
But
she lies in this
tomb costing thousands of yuan per square meter.
My sister believed in you until her death.
Why did you choose Lu Qianqian?
My encounter with Qianqian was an accident.
But this accident indirectly killed her.
How dare you sit in
the chairman's chair?
It's just a chair.
I'll sit for a while.
Shh.
Ouch.
What are you doing?
Shh.
Don't talk.
Get down.
No.
Stand here.
Stand here and don't move.
What were you doing just now?
Saving you.
Our chairman
hates it when others sit in her chair.
The last person who sat in her chair
is still mining in Cambodia.
You must be the new intern Xixi mentioned.
Why are you laughing?
I just find you interesting.
Oh.
Don't wear Chanel clothes
at the company anymore.
Why?
The company doesn't have a dress code.
I heard the young lady is coming back
and will be working at the company.
So what?
What I wear doesn't affect her.
You really don't know anything, do you?
You...
The...
The young lady loves Chanel clothes the most.
What you're doing is basically suicide.
Suicide, you know?
That crazy woman
She splashed wine on her dress twin.
Later, I heard she even stuffed that person in the trunk.
Just because they wore the same dress.
Where did you hear these rumors?
My colleagues at the company.
They all say so.
Suddenly I realize
you're quite concerned about me, an intern.
We're all new to the workplace.
I think as long as we can be colleagues,
it's fate.
I'll help you if I can.
A friend in need is a friend indeed.
Hello.
I'm Zhou Jian.
I'm
Chen Qianqian.
Oh.
You just came to the company.
I have to remind you of something.